[
  {
    "question": "[\u0020]",
    "answer": "U+0020",
    "description": "Space"
  },
  {
    "question": "[\u00A0]",
    "answer": "U+00A0",
    "description": "Non-break Space"
  },
  {
    "question": "[\u2000]",
    "answer": "U+2000",
    "description": "En Quad"
  },
  {
    "question": "[\u2001]",
    "answer": "U+2001",
    "description": "Em Quad"
  },
  {
    "question": "[\u2002]",
    "answer": "U+2002",
    "description": "En Space"
  },
  {
    "question": "[\u2003]",
    "answer": "U+2003",
    "description": "Em Space"
  },
  {
    "question": "[\u2004]",
    "answer": "U+2004",
    "description": "Three-Per-Em Space"
  },
  {
    "question": "[\u2005]",
    "answer": "U+2005",
    "description": "Four-Per-Em Space"
  },
  {
    "question": "[\u2006]",
    "answer": "U+2006",
    "description": "Six-Per-Em Space"
  },
  {
    "question": "[\u2007]",
    "answer": "U+2007",
    "description": "Figure Space"
  },
  {
    "question": "[\u2008]",
    "answer": "U+2008",
    "description": "Punctuation Space"
  },
  {
    "question": "[\u2009]",
    "answer": "U+2009",
    "description": "Thin Space"
  },
  {
    "question": "[\u200A]",
    "answer": "U+200A",
    "description": "Hair Space"
  },
  {
    "question": "[\u2028]",
    "answer": "U+2028",
    "description": "Line Separator"
  },
  {
    "question": "[\u205F]",
    "answer": "U+205F",
    "description": "Medium Mathematical Space"
  },
  {
    "question": "[\u3000]",
    "answer": "U+3000",
    "description": "Ideographic Space"
  }
]

